real-debrid.com 2018-07-30

# Real-Debrid

## Privacy Policy

The Site © Real-Debrid is edited by the company

 **XT Network SARL** _(Siret 53012531900018)_ ,  
39 Rue des Granges Galand,  
37550 Saint Avertin,  
FRANCE.

This privacy policy may be changed at any time.

Agreement relating to confidentiality. 

#### IP Addresses recording and their geolocations

Our servers can detect the IP Address of Users connection through the Internet. These IP addresses and their geolocations are recorded by our servers for internal use only (registration on the site, optimal use of downloads, protection against thieves, etc.).

#### Email addresses recording

Our server stores the email addresses of Users during registration for internal purposes only. Under no circumstances, we will rent, sell, or send personal data's to third parties.

#### Use of cookies

We use cookies for Users convenience by saving the connection to the site (thus avoiding unnecessary reconnections). We do not use tracking methods.

#### Payment Informations

All payments made on our website are managed by outside firms. Payments are secure and encrypted, in any case these companies can not save Users banking information.

#### Exceptional disclosure of personal data

We may be required to disclose Users personal data in order to protect our legal rights or where disclosure of Users personal data's are required of us by the judicial authorities only when legal procedures are followed.

#### Advertisments

The advertisements on our website are offered by other companies. They can use information about Users visits in order to target content which will potentially interest Users (Name, mailing address, etc. are excluded from these data). 

#### Datalogging

Files links that Users download are stored in a database for legal concerns and our internal use. All saved links are erased within 1 month for security reasons and service needs. However all requests made on our site are stored for 1 year, the legal retention period.
